MIKE : I got the Strangler . Wabash and Van Buren .
( SIREN BLARING )
( GUN FIRES )
Oh , shit .
Oh , shit !
MIKE : Jack , get the van .
Eddie , help me !
Eddie , Eddie , don 't leave me ! God , no !
Give it up , Ray . It 's over .
( ALARM RINGING )
( GROANS )
Oh , God , I 'm dying .
( SHOUTING ) You hear this , you son of a bitch ?
( CHARLES COUGHING )
I 'm gonna get you for it !
I 'm gonna get you , and I 'm gonna get Eddie ,
no matter what !
( PANTING )
I gotta find somebody .
I don 't know . I gotta find somebody .
Gotta find somebody .
( LAUGHS )
CHARLES : Ade due damballa .
Give me the power , I beg of you !
( THUNDER RUMBLING )
Secoise entienne mais pois de morte .
Morteisma lieu de vocuier de mieu vochette
Endonline pour de boisette damballa !
Secoise entienne mais pois de morte .
Endelieu pour de boisette damballa !
Endelieu pour de boisette damballa .
( CHARLES SCREAMING )
( SCREAMS )
( CHUCKY 'S ANIMATED THEME PLAYING ON TV )
BOY 1 ON TV : I have no friends . No one will play with me .
BOY 2 ON TV : Uh-oh ,
There 's a friend in need .
Hey , cheer up .
BOY 1 ON TV : Who are you ? BOY 2 ON TV : I 'm a Good Guy .
I 've just come from the Good Guy Clubhouse ,
and I 'll be your friend to the end .
BOY 1 ON TV : You will ? You mean you 'll be my friend now ?
BOY 2 ON TV : Sure , I will ,
Hidey-ho .
( BOY 2 LAUGHS )
I saw this one .
KIDS ON TV : ( SINGING ) Hidey hidey ho Best friends till the end
When you 're feeling down or feeling blue
A Good Guy will always be there for you
Because a Good Guy is your true blue friend
He 's your best friend till the end
MAN ON TV : All right , good guys , that 's our " Good Guys " show for today ,
but don 't go away ,
because we 've got a very important Good Guy message just for you .
MASCOT ON TV : Hi , Good Guys . Boy , have I got news for you .
Now you can have your very own Good Guy doll .
That 's right .
You can have all the adventures we have on TV in your very own home .
Good Guys say three different sentences .
We even turn our heads and blink our eyes when you talk to us .
Right , Oscar ?
Hi , I 'm Oscar , and I 'm your friend to the end . Hidey-ho .
( LAUGHING )
Wow !
MASCOT : Every Good Guy has a name all his own ,
so he can be your very own best friend .
So remember to tell Mom and Dad you want a Good Guy .
Perfect for birthdays or just any old time .
And remember , you can buy all of our Good Guy accessories , too .
- Right , Oscar ? - Right .
( BOTH LAUGHING )
MAN ON TV : Brought to you exclusively by Play Pals ,
makers of Good Guys and other fine toys .
Found in toy stores throughout the greater Chicago area .
Mommy , wake up .
Mommy .
- Wake up , Mommy . Wake up . - Andy .
What time is it , Andy ?
- Wake up . - 6 : 30 . It 's only 6 : 30 in the morning .
( GROANS )
But it 's a beautiful day outside . See ?
It certainly is .
- How long you been up , birthday boy ? - Since forever .
I made you breakfast in bed .
You did ? Oh , God .
Well , thanks .
Well , this looks just excellent .
I 'll tell you what .
Why don 't I eat this just a little later , okay ?
Mmm-hmm .
But first , I gotta give you your super-duper birthday tummy-gummy .
Come here . Come here . Come here .
( BLOWING RASPBERRY )
That 's one . How many years old are you today ? Two .
Happy birthday , pumpkin .
Thanks . Can we open my presents now , Mommy ?
- Yes , we can . - Terrific !
FEMALE ANNOUNCER ON TV : Good morning , Chicago . Leading off at this hour ,
Charles Lee Ray , the notorious Lake Shore Strangler was shot and killed
shortly before 3 : 00 a.m. this morning on Wabash Avenue .
Can I open this first , Mommy ? Can I , can I ?
Andy , don 't you want to start with the smaller one first ?
Okay , go ahead .
Well , what do you think ? You need these clothes so badly .
Hey , I think they 're gonna be okay .
We 'll just have to take them up just a couple of inches .
- What 's the matter ? - Nothing .
Oh , I know . You want some toys , don 't you ?
Not boring old clothes .
Try the other one .
- Well , what do you think ? - I want a Good Guy to go with it .
I know you do , Andy .
But I didn 't know about it in time this month to save up for it .
- Karen . - Hi .
You know that doll that you wanted for Andy ?
- The one that costs 100 bucks ? - Yeah , the Good Guy doll .
There is a peddler in the alley behind the store , and I think he 's got one .
What ? What would a peddler be doing with a doll ?
Who cares ? Would you grab your purse and come on ? We can get a deal on it .
- But I can 't just leave my counter . - Do you want the damn doll or don 't you ?
- Of course I do . - Well , then , come on .
- Come on . - All right .
There he is .
Okay , show her .
Well , is it a Good Guy or not ?
It is . It is .
- Yeah , well , I told you . - How much do you want for it ?
50 bucks .
- 10 and not a penny more . - 30 .
What , are you kidding ? That thing is not worth $ 30 .
No . Take it or leave it . Somebody else will buy it .
- I 'll take it . - Karen , it 's too much money .
No , it isn 't . You have no idea how much Andy wants this doll .
But we don 't even know if the damn thing works .
Here you go , lady . May it bring you and your kid a lot of joy .
KAREN : Thank you .
Hey , hold on , you !
How do we know the damn thing isn 't stolen ?
- Steal this . - MAGGIE : Steal this yourself .
- ( LAUGHING ) Maggie . - I think I dated him .
Come on . We gotta get back to work .
Andy 's gonna love it !
Mrs. Barclay , so nice of you to drop by . Have a nice break ?
I 'm sorry , Mr. Criswell . I was only gone for a minute .
Have a heart , Criswell .
We were just downstairs buying her little boy a birthday present .
We have specified break times for activities like that , Miss Peterson .
Mrs. Howe has taken sick , and we 're shorthanded tonight .
You 'll have to fill in for her .
I can 't . I have to pick up my son at the day care center in an hour .
- I 'm sorry , this is an emergency . - Wait a second . I 'll take over for her .
Miss Peterson , you work in shoes , not in jewelry .
You 'll just simply have to do it .
Now , you can take off at 5 : 00 , but you 'll have to be back at 7 : 00 .
It 's my son 's birthday .
Mrs. Barclay , are you happy with your job here ?
Yes , of course I am .
- Then I suggest that ... - Hey .
Chill out , would you , Walter ?
- I 'll take care of Andy for you . - Maggie , you can 't do it again .
Don 't be silly . It 'll be the hottest date I 've had in months .
I can 't imagine why .
- Hey , where are you going ? - Good Guys are on TV .
Well , I may have something better for you .
What ?
This isn 't groceries .
A Good Guy ! I knew it !
I knew you 'd get me one .
Show me how he works , okay ?
Hi , I 'm Andy . What 's your name ?
Hi , I 'm Chucky , and I 'm your friend to the end . Hidey-ho .
( CHUCKY LAUGHS )
Wow ! He 's something , isn 't he ?
Oh , Mom , thanks .
You 're welcome , honey .
( MAN CHATTERING ON TV )
( TAPPING )
( HUMMING )
See , that 's how you build things .
MALE ANNOUNCER ON TV : Good evening . WDOL with a late breaking report .
Eddie Caputo , repeated accomplice of Charles Lee Ray ,
has just escaped the Michigan Avenue precinct .
More details to follow on the news at 9 : 00 next .
Hey , Chucky , you 're not watching me .
Hey , wanna play ?
Hey , it 's time for bed , Andy .
MAN ON TV : No , sir . Never saw the little swab before .
Come on , Chucky . We have to get ready to go to bed .
BOY ON TV : I 'm not a stowaway . Mr. Ghoo brought me here .
MAN : And who might Mr. Apple be ?
Aunt Maggie , Chucky wants to watch the 9 : 00 news .
Sure he does .
Okay , kid , off we go .
Come on . There we go .
- Chucky . - Oh , yes , Chucky .
You , too . Off we go .
Now , it 's brush your teeth and under the covers with you .
Okay ? Agreed ?
Good . Okay .
You yell when you 're ready for me to tuck you in .
Hey , Chucky , want to see my room ?
( HUMMING )
Andy , are you brushing your teeth ?
Yes , Aunt Maggie .
Good .
ANNOUNCER ON TV : And now , Action News at 9 : 00 .
TERRY : In Washington today ,
the mayor replied that he would study the congressional findings carefully
and have the commission on gang-related violence issue recommendations to him .
Back to you , Steve .
STEVE : Thank you , Terry .
In other news , police have now clarified the information
regarding the escape of Eddie Caputo .
Authorities say that Caputo managed to elude his captors
while being transferred onto a prison bus on his way to court . Of course ...
Okay , mister , what do you have to say about this ?
- About what ? - Come on . Come on .
You know , you have to learn that when I say something , I mean it .
- But what did I do ? - You know what I 'm talking about .
Turning the TV on and putting Chucky in front of it
when I told you it was time to go to bed .
- I didn 't do that . - Oh , no ? What did Chucky do ?
Walk into the living room and turn it on all by himself ?
Did you do that , Chucky ?
Andy , stop it . Now , come on , under the covers . Hurry .
- But , Auntie ... - Under the covers and not another word .
But I didn 't put Chucky in front of the TV .
Enough . Okay ?
Give me a kiss .
Good night , baby , and happy birthday .
Good night , Aunt Maggie .
( DOOR CLOSING )
I told you she 'd be mad at you if you watched the news .
MAN ON TV : I missed you , my dear .
I was afraid you weren 't going to show up .
Too bad about the accident .
WOMAN ON TV : Yes . Papa told us they just found it .
Haw did you know ?
MAN : I must have heard it somewhere .
WOMAN : I haven 't seen you in so long , darling .
I mean , couldn 't we take a little walk , or something ?
It looks as though you haven 't had a breath of fresh air in days .
MAN : A walk ? WOMAN : Of course .
The air outside will do you good . Besides , you 'll work up an appetite .
Please .
MAN : But , Janice , surely it 's going to rain .
( GASPS )
Andy ?
MAN : Depends on whether there 's an indictment .
WOMAN : Well , they don 't always ...
( THUDDING )
Andy , is that you ?
( THUNDER CRASHING )
( BANGING )
( SCREAMS )
How did that happen ?
( PHONE RINGS )
Uh ... Hello ?
Hi . How 's it going ? How 's Andy ?
MAGGIE : Karen ?
Yeah . Who else would it be ? Is something wrong ?
Uh ...
No .
( CHUCKLING )
Everything 's fine .
Are you sure ? You don 't sound like everything 's fine .
No , I just had a bit of the alone-at-night willies . You know ?
Now , would you stop worrying
and give Criswell a kick in the pants for me ?
( LAUGHING )
You got it .
Hey , listen , Maggie . Thank you for everything .
You 're a real pal .
Oh , yeah ?
Yeah , yeah . Give Andy a kiss for me , will you ? See you soon . Bye .
( CLINKING )
What is wrong with me ?
I 'm scaring myself half to death .
( SCREAMING )
POLICEMAN 1 : Step away from this barricade .
Come on , move it back . There 's nothing to see .
POLICEMAN 2 : Now , let 's move this police line back here .
Go on home , folks , please .
DETECTIVE : She was on the sixth floor .
- Miss , what do you think you 're doing ? - I live here .
Andy ?
Oh , no . Andy ?
Andy !
Mommy !
Oh , thank God .
Are you all right ?
Oh , I 'm so glad . I got so scared when I ...
What 's wrong ? Where 's Maggie ?
- She had an accident . - Accident ? What kind of an accident ?
Mrs. Barclay , I 'm Detective Mike Norris , Homicide .
Could I talk to you out in the hall ?
- Why ? What 's happened to Maggie ? - Please ?
I 'll be right back .
Look , Mrs. Barclay ...
What ?
- Miss Peterson 's dead , Mrs. Barclay . - What ?
- How ? - She fell from your kitchen window .
Oh , no .
You all right ?
- Yes . - All right .
Come on .
Oh , Maggie .
Did you check over here ?
( CRYING )
Oh , Maggie .
You got any idea what these are ?
No .
MIKE : They look like footprints , don 't they ? Very small footprints .
What are you implying ?
I don 't know . What would Andy be doing up on the counter , right ?
- What ? - Besides ,
I already checked his closet . None of his shoes matched these prints .
Mommy ? Mommy ?
Chucky wanted to know what was going on .
Andy , I want you to go to bed . The detective and I are very busy .
- But , Mom ... - Right now , please .
MIKE : Andy .
What do you got on your feet ?
Good Guy PJ sneakers .
Wow . Come here .
- Can I see the bottoms of them ? - Sure .
Look at this . There 's a gun . Is that a cowboy hat ?
Andy , get into bed . I 'll be in in a minute to tuck you in .
- But , Mom ... - Right now .
Why are you treating Andy like this ?
If he says he doesn 't know how those footprints got there , then he doesn 't .
Look , Mrs. Barclay , somebody made those footprints . If not Andy , then who ?
I don 't know , and I don 't care .
All I know is that I 've just lost my best friend tonight to a horrible accident
and I would like some time alone with my son ,
who I 'm sure is just as upset about this as I am .
Okay . Sorry . I 'm sorry .
I 'll clear everybody out of here right away . Okay ?
Hey , guys , you done ? Let 's go . Chop-chop .
Let 's go , everybody . Out of here .
POLICEMAN 1 : Let 's clear this up over here . Come on .
POLICEMAN 2 : Okay .
POLICEMAN 3 : Let 's go , Sid .
What do you think was so important about my sneakers , Chucky ?
You don 't know either , do you ?
Well , let me know if you find out anything about those footprints .
Mommy , Mommy .
Mommy , I know who was on the kitchen counter . I know , I know .
- Andy , I thought I ... - Who , Andy ? Who ?
Chucky !
Your doll ?
KAREN : Andy , that 's enough stories for tonight .
Now , come on , back to bed . Now I mean it .
But , Mom ...
Good night , Detective .
- What ? - Are you gonna call me ?
- You don 't give up , do you ? - I just ... I hate loose ends .
And I hate people who don 't know when to stop .
( WHISTLES )
Ouch .
- A spirited lady . - No kidding .
I want that autopsy report on my desk
- first thing tomorrow . - Yeah .
And anything you can find out about Mrs. Barclay and her son .
You got it . Anything else I can do for you , sir ?
Oh , yeah . Here . Get this to the lab .
I found it in the corner of the kitchen .
- What is this ? - Possible murder weapon .
No .
Come on . You 're kidding me .
Hey , you are kidding me , aren 't you ?
ANDY : ' Cause she saw you walking and talking ?
I guess there was no hiding from her .
Andy , who are you talking to ?
Chucky .
Chucky , huh ?
Yeah , sure , Chucky .
He 's sitting right over there .
Chucky 's been talking to you , too , hasn 't he ?
- What 's he been saying ? - All kinds of things .
His real name is Charles Lee Ray ,
and he 's been sent down from heaven by Daddy to play with me .
He has , has he ? Anything else ?
Yes . He said Aunt Maggie was a real bitch
and got what she deserved .
Andy , how can you say something so horrible ?
I didn 't say it . Chucky did .
Andy , stop it . You know perfectly well that you 're making this up .
But I 'm not . Chucky 's alive ...
- Really , he is . - Andy , Chucky ... Chucky 's a doll .
He 's made of plastic and stuffing .
Look at him . Look at him .
Now , does he look like anything else to you ?
Don 't , you 'll hurt him .
Andy , look !
Now you don 't really think that Chucky is alive , do you ?
But he is .
Andy , stop it . Please .
It 's ' cause of Aunt Maggie you 're yelling at me , isn 't it ?
Yes . Yes , I guess it is .
I 'm sorry .
I 'll stop making up stories .
Thanks , champ .
Do you wanna sleep in with me tonight ?
No , it 's all right .
I 've got Chucky .
Come on , into bed .
Good night , sweetheart .
I love you .
Good night .
You 're right , Chucky . She didn 't believe me .
Hi . I like to be hugged .
Good . I 'd love to hug you , too .
( SCHOOL BELL RINGING )
Hey .
You sure you 're all right about last night ?
No bad dreams about Aunt Maggie ?
And Chucky 's only a doll , right ?
All right , off to school with you , then . I love you tons .
MAN ON PA : 43rd street . Next stop , 47th .
Is that Eddie 's ?
Look , you stay here . I have to go tinkle .
I 'll be right there , Chucky .
( CHUCKY PANTING )
( THUDDING )
( GAS HISSING )
Chucky ?
( GUN COCKING )
( CLANGING )
( GASPS )
Chucky ?
( CRASHING )
( GAS HISSING )
Chucky ?
Mrs. Barclay .
Detective Norris , I came as soon as I got your message .
You haven 't been to the school to pick up your son yet ?
- No . No , I came directly from work . Why ? - Let 's go into my office .
- Is something wrong with Andy ? - Please .
I ...
I don 't know how to tell you this , Mrs. Barclay .
Tell me what ?
Do you have any idea why your Aunt Maggie fell out of that window ?
- Yes . - Could you tell me why ?
'Cause she saw Chucky , and it scared her so much , she fell out .
Oh , she did , huh ?
( DOOR OPENING )
So why did Chucky go to see Eddie Caputo ?
Mommy !
Oh , Andy .
All right , sweetheart . Come on .
Now listen to me , okay ?
Nobody believes you about Chucky .
Unless you start telling the truth right now ,
they 're going to take you away from me .
You hear that , Chucky ?
They 're taking me away unless you say something .
Please , say something .
Come on , Chucky . Say something .
Tell me why you lied to me about everything .
Tell me .
Hi , I 'm Chucky , and I 'm your friend to the end . Hidey-ho .
( CHUCKY LAUGHS )
( GRUNTS )
Mommy , he 's doing it on purpose .
He told me never to tell about him or he 'd kill me .
Mrs. Barclay , my name is Dr. Ardmore . I 'm from County General .
I 've seen more than enough .
Maybe Andy should spend a couple of days with us .
Well , say something , you little bastard .
Say something , damn it !
Hi . I like to be hugged .
( LAUGHING )
" He wants you for a best friend . "
Yeah , sure .
Hi , I 'm Chucky . Wanna play ?
( SCREAMS )
Talk to me .
Come on , talk .
I said , talk to me , damn it . All right .
Then I 'm gonna make you talk !
I said talk to me , damn it , or else I am gonna throw you in the fire !
You stupid bitch ! You filthy slut !
- I 'll teach you to fuck with me ! - No ! No !
( SCREAMING )
( CHUCKY GRUNTING )
( GROANS )
( SCREAMING )
( EXCLAIMS )
( DOOR OPENING )
KAREN : Stop !
No .
( SOBBING )
No !
Detective Norris !
Mrs. Barclay , what are you doing back here ?
Andy was telling the truth . Chucky is alive and he killed Eddie Caputo .
- What ? - I took him home to my apartment .
I was about to throw away the box that he came in when the batteries fell out .
Don 't you see ?
He 's been moving and talking for days without any batteries in him .
- What are you talking about ? - How I found out the doll was alive .
See , I threatened to throw him into the fireplace ,
when all of a sudden , he came alive in my hand .
I dropped him , and he got up and ran out of the apartment .
Good night , Mrs. Barclay .
Wait a minute . I am telling you the truth .
He killed Maggie . He killed Eddie Caputo .
Look , Mrs. Barclay . I sympathize with you . I really do .
I hated what happened in there today .
- But lying is not gonna help your son . - Lying ? Does this look like I 'm lying ?
- How did you get those ? - Chucky bit me .
Oh , for God 's sake .
All right , don 't believe me .
- Where you going ? - To find Chucky .
How you gonna do that ?
I bought him from a peddler where I work . I 'll start there .
That isn 't a good part of town to be in at this time of night .
Mrs. Barclay , do you hear me ?
You don 't want to go down there at this time of night .
God damn it .
( INAUDIBLE )
What 's she doing here ?
Hey , excuse me .
Mister .
I 'm not gonna hurt you . Do you remember me ?
- No , no . - I 'm sorry . I bought a doll from you
in back of Carson 's department store with my friend yesterday .
- Doll ? - Yes , a Good Guy doll .
- You sold it to me . Do you remember ? - Oh , yeah , a doll . What about it ?
Where did you get it ?
What will you give me if I tell you ?
I don 't have much , but you 're welcome to whatever I have .
It 's not enough . What else you got ?
- That 's all I 've got . - All you got ?
- What are you ... Yes . - That 's not all you got .
- Wait a minute . - No , you got a lot .
No . No , no .
( SCREAMING ) No . Wait . No , no !
Pig !
- Christ , he 's a cop ! - All right . What about the rest of you ?
You wanna party , too ?
All right . Now , you want to answer the lady 's question now ?
- Where did you get the doll from ? - I don 't know nothing about no doll .
You 're not gonna know nothing about nothing in a minute ,
unless you talk to me . Now talk !
A burned-out toy store on Wabash . That 's where I got it .
Get out of here .
What 's wrong ?
Nothing .
Well , wait a minute . Something the peddler said upset you . What was it ?
I just told you , nothing .
God damn it . My son 's life is at stake . Now , what was it ?
The place where he said he got the doll , Charles Lee Ray died there .
Who ?
The Lake Shore Strangler . The man who 's partners with Eddie Caputo .
- Hey . Where are you going now ? - Wabash and Van Buren .
There 's nothing there . It 's an abandoned wreck of a store .
Why don 't you believe me ?
It was struck by lightning the night that Charles Lee Ray died .
How do you know that ?
Because I was there . I was the man who killed him .
Why didn 't you tell me ?
It 's not exactly the kind of thing you tell someone .
Come on , let me take you home . You need some sleep .
Did he say anything ? Anything at all ?
- Who ? - Charles Lee Ray .
Yeah . He threatened to kill me and Eddie Caputo .
I 'm sorry you couldn 't find anything to help Andy .
I really am .
But I did . I found out that Chucky is Charles Lee Ray .
The only thing I don 't know is how he got inside the doll .
- Good night , Mrs. Barclay . - Where did Charles Lee Ray live ?
Look , please , will you just get out of the car ?
Hey , just tell me where he lived .
Don 't you understand ? Andy 's life depends on it .
730 Stoney Island , the south side .
But I 've already checked the place out . There 's nothing there . Now , good night .
Wait a minute . Where are you going ?
- Home , to get some sleep . - No , you can 't do that .
Don 't you see ? You just said it .
Chucky killed Caputo . That leaves you .
- That does it . - Please listen to me .
- Out . - I am telling you the truth .
Why won 't you believe me ?
Because I 'm sane , Mrs. Barclay . Sane and rational .
All right . All right .
Do you remember what you said the first night you met me in my apartment ?
- What about it ? - You said you didn 't like loose ends .
Well , I 'm a loose end .
You can 't just let go what I said tonight without checking it out .
For the last time , Mrs. Barclay , good night .
( GRUNTS IN ANNOYANCE )
( STARTS ENGINE )
MAN ON RADIO : ( SINGING ) I go outside
Don 't you lift the top
When you want to see inside
You can only see one thing
At a time and that won 't ...
( SCREAMS )
Good night , asshole .
( LAUGHING )
( SCREAMING )
( CHOKING )
( SCREAMS )
MAN : Jeez , look out !
Hi , Mikey .
( GROWLING )
( CHUCKY LAUGHS )
Won 't do you any good , Mikey . You can 't hurt me .
( GUN FIRES )
( CHUCKY LAUGHING )
( SCREAMING )
( GUN FIRES )
( SIGHS )
- Karen . - ( SCREAMS )
( EXHALES )
What are you doing here ?
After I talked to you last night ,
I decided to go back to the station and pull Ray 's file .
I learned a couple of things . His nickname was Chucky ,
and he spent a lot of time with this man .
Now , all we have to do is find him before Chucky does .
CHUCKY : Hello , John .
Over here .
Hi .
It 's me . Chucky .
What do you think ? The grigri work ?
You know , when I came here learning all that stuff about how to beat death ,
I thought maybe you were pulling my chain .
But not now . Not now .
- Only one problem . - What ?
This . I didn 't think anybody could hurt me .
But last night , I got shot .
You know something ? It hurt .
It hurt like a son of a bitch . It even bled .
Now why 's that , John ?
- You 're turning human . - What ?
The more time you spend in that body ,
the more human you 'll become .
You mean I have to live out the rest of my life in this body ?
No fucking way . You got me into this , you get me out .
- I can 't do that , Chucky . - Why not ?
Because you 're an abomination ,
an outrage against nature .
You perverted everything I 've taught you and used it for evil .
And you have to be stopped .
You know , I thought something like this might happen .
- That 's why I prepared for it . - What are you talking about ?
Your own personal mojo , doc .
- Give me that . - Sure . How do you want it ? Broken leg ?
( SCREAMS )
Shouldn 't tell your customers where you hide things like this , John .
Gets you in trouble every time .
Now how do I get out of this body ?
- No , I won 't tell you . - Yeah ?
( SCREAMS )
Tell me or die , John . Your choice .
No , I 'll tell you .
You have to transfer your soul out of the doll
into that of the first human being you revealed your true self to .
You mean the first person I let in on the fact that I was really alive ?
( LAUGHING )
I don 't believe it . I just don 't believe it .
The first person I let in on my little secret was a six-year-old kid .
I 'm gonna be six years old again .
Well , John , it 's been fun , but I gotta go .
I have a date with a six-year-old boy .
And you have a date with death .
( GROANING )
So long , John .
( SIREN BLARING )
Hold it . Wait , wait .
Oh , my God .
( DIALING )
- Too late . - What ?
Must save the boy . Must ...
Must get his soul
into him like he got into doll .
What ?
You must stop him before he can say the chant .
Kill him before he can say it .
But how ? How ?
The heart . His heart is almost human .
It 's the only way . Through the heart .
( CLANGING )
Help me ! Help me ! Dr. Ardmore , Chucky 's here !
Help me ! He 's coming to kill me ! He 's here . Chucky 's here .
I don 't see anybody .
But , Doctor , Chucky 's here ,
and he 's going to kill me .
But Chucky is here , and he 's going to kill me !
He 's going to kill me .
Please don 't leave me . Please .
( CRYING )
( IS IT REALLY LOVE PLAYING ON RADIO )
( GASPS )
No !
ARDMORE : Andy , stop . ATTENDANT : Hey , wait a minute .
Stop him !
MAN : Check the north corridor .
( SCREAMING )
( ANDY SCREAMS )
Easy . Easy , it 's all right , Andy . It 's all right .
You 're not gonna need this anymore , all right ?
But I do . Chucky 's in the room , and he 's trying to kill me .
No , Andy . It 's gonna be all right . I 'm here now .
And I 'm gonna protect you .
Andy . Easy , boy . Easy .
Come on , nobody 's here .
- No , please . He 'll kill you , too . - Andy , now ...
No , please . Listen to me . Please .
Andy , now this is just gonna sting you for one second .
( SCREAMS )
( ZAPPING )
Stop ! Stop ! Stop ! Stop !
( LAUGHS )
Stop .
What happened ?
Look , miss , could you just excuse us for a minute here , all right ?
What ?
- What ? - Yeah , yeah .
Fried him to a crisp with the electric shock machine and then he escaped .
Escaped ? Where ?
We don 't know , but I bet she does .
Chucky . You seen Chucky anywhere ?
- Who 's Chucky ? - Kid 's doll .
The same one that was at the station house .
Have you seen him anywhere ?
What am I gonna know about a doll ? Where are you going ?
They think Andy did it .
I know , the girl said that Chucky was here , and that he was looking for Andy .
- But where would Andy go ? - He 'd go home .
I always told him to go there if he was in trouble .
- Does he have a key ? - It 's under the mat .
Come on . Come on . We don 't have much time .
Look , George . Some child left their doll in the elevator .
Leave it alone . Whoever left it there will come back looking for it .
Ugly doll .
CHUCKY : Fuck you .
( SHOUTS )
Surprise !
( ANDY GRUNTS )
Batter up !
( GROANS )
( SIREN BLARING )
Ade due damballa .
Valinchella santeria
Oya shungo yenya macumba .
Give me the power , I beg of you .
Leveau mercier du bois chio .
Secoise entienne mais pois de morte .
KAREN : Andy !
- Morteisme lieu ... - Andy !
MIKE : Andy ! KAREN : Andy !
MIKE : Andy , can you hear me ?
Secoise entienne mais pois de morte .
Morteisme lieu de vocuier de mieu vochette .
- Andy ! - Endelieu pour de boisette damba ...
( SCREAMING )
KAREN : Andy .
MIKE : Karen , Karen , are you all right ?
( SCREAMS )
Oh , Mike .
Just take care of Andy .
Karen , Karen .
- Take this . Take it . - Mike !
( WHIMPERING )
Mommy .
( SCREAMS )
( CLICKING )
CHUCKY : What 's wrong ? Gun jammed ?
( SCREAMING )
Andy !
Andy , help me . The matches .
Please ! Now !
Andy , no , please .
We 're friends to the end . Remember ?
This is the end , friend .
( SCREAMING )
( GASPS )
Oh , my baby .
MIKE : Karen ? Andy ? You all right ?
( GROANING )
Andy , go get me the first-aid kit under the kitchen sink really fast . Okay ?
- What happened ? - Oh , God . Chucky 's dead .
( CRASHING )
Mommy , Chucky 's gone .
KAREN : Andy , hurry up .
Andy .
Hello , Andy .
Mommy .
Mommy !
( SCREAMS )
Give me the boy , and I 'll let you live .
Do you hear me ? Give me the boy .
( KAREN SCREAMING )
Mommy !
( SCREAMING )
( CRYING )
CHUCKY : Give me the boy .
( GASPS )
( CLICKING )
JOHN : What the hell 's going on here ?
- Oh , hey , hey , hey . - MIKE : Karen .
Oh , Jesus .
Yeah , I got a cop down here . Multiple stab wounds .
The Brewster Apartments on North Grand Street . Make it fast .
All right , they 're gonna be here in 10 minutes . Now , tell me what happened .
The kid was right . The doll 's alive .
- He almost got the three of us . - Come on , what are you talking about ?
You don 't believe me ? All right , well , go on . Check it out in the hall .
It 's scattered all over the place . But don 't touch it .
Do you understand me ? Don 't you touch one part of it !
All right , look . Take it easy , okay ? Just relax yourself , all right ? All right .
Okay , Mike . I 'd like you to take a look at this thing , okay ?
Because there 's no way this thing 's alive .
- I thought I told you not to touch it . - Mike , will you be sensible ?
Come on , look . It 's as dead as they come . It 's dead .
( SCREAMS )
CHUCKY : Choke him ! Kill him !
Rip his throat out .
Kill him !
Kill him .
Kill him now ! Strangle him ! Don 't let go !
God .
Kill ' em ! Kill ' em ! Kill ' em all !
The heart . Shoot him in the heart .
( SCREAMS )
Hi , I 'm Chucky .
Wanna play ?
- You believe me now ? - Yeah .
But who 's gonna believe me ?
( SIREN BLARING )
Come on .
JOHN : All right . Ready ? Here we go .
Andy .
Come on . We 're gonna go to the hospital with Mike .
Let 's go .